<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Guide app</string>
    <string name="admob_app_id">123</string>
    <string name="infoper">A Personal Loan has flexible repayment terms and usually no security or collateral is required. Here is a five-step guide on how to get a Personal Loan. From documents required to how to apply for a PersonaLoan, we have all the angles covered: Step\n1: Determine your requirement Figure out why you need a Personal Loan and how much you need. For example, you may need a loan to fund your wedding or to renovate your home. And you may need just Rs. 1 lac or Rs. 10 lac. Step 2: Check loan eligibility Once you know how much you need, you should check whether you are eligible. You can visit the HDFC Bank Personal Loan Eligibility Calculator online, to find out ow much you can borrow as Personal oan. HDFC Bank offers loans up to Rs. 0 lac. Read more about how to calculateyour Personal Loan EMI and how to lower  t. Step 3: Calculate monthly instalments se an online EMI tool to calculate your pproximate loan repayments every month. ou can modify the interest rate and tenure o match your monthly income, like on DFC Bank Personal Loan EMI calculator.HDFC Bank offers pocket friendly EMIs n all its Personal Loan starting at Rs. 878 per lac * (T&amp;C). Step 4: Approach the ank You can apply for a Personal Loan ith HDFC Bank in a variety of ,  one website, at an ATM or by visiting a branch.Step 5: Submit documents Next find out hat documents are required for a Personal oan. Usually, you will need income proof bank statements, salary slips or IT returns), ddress proof and ID proof. Hand over opies of your Personal Loan documents t the bank. Wait for funds to be remittedto your account. HDFC Bank disburses unds for pre-approved loans to customersin 10 seconds*, and for non-HDFC Bank</string>
    <string name="personaloaninfo">Personal loans can be used for any personal expenses and don\'t have a designated purpose. This makes them an attractive option for people with outstanding debts, such as credit card debt, who want to reduce their interest rates by transferring balances. Like other loans, personal loan terms depend on your credit history. \nA personal loan is an amount of money you can borrow to use for a variety of purposes. For instance, you may use a personal loan to consolidate debt, pay for home renovations, or plan a dream wedding. Personal loans can be offered by banks, credit unions, or online lenders. The money you borrow must be repaid over time, typically with interest. Some lenders may also charge fees for personal loans. A personal loan is also different from a personal line of credit. The latter is not a lump sum amount; instead, it works like a credit card. You have a credit line that you can spend money against and, as you do so, your available credit is reduced. You can then free up available credit by making a payment toward your credit line.</string>
    <string name="newtxt">Aadhar Card loans can be used for any personal expenses and don\'t have a designated purpose. This makes them an attractive option for people with outstandingdebts, such as credit card debt, who want to reduce their interest rates by transferring  balances. Like other loans, personal loan terms depend on your credit history. The money you borrow must be repaid over time typically with interest. Some lenders may also charge fees for personal loans. An Aadhar loan is also different from a personal line of credit. The latter is not a lump sum amount; instead, it works like a credit card. You have a credit line that you can spend money against and, as you do so, your available credit is reduced. You can then free up available credit by making a payment toward your credit line. </string>
    <string name="loan_finance_planner"><![CDATA[Loan & Finance Planner]]></string>
    <string name="txt">You can avail a Startup business loan from a bank or afinancial body in order to raise funds to start a business of your own or expand your current business. The rate of interest charged by the bank will depend on the loan amount availed by you and the repayment tenure There are more than 39,000 startups in India at present who have access to many private equity and debt funding options. However, it is a challenge to get funding when the business is just an idea or is in the early stage. Also, the Micro, Small, and Medium Enterprises (MSME) sector in India only has limited access to formal credit which is why the Government of India decided to roll out startup busin in schemes for MSMEs and startups.\nThis is a digital platform which allows you to avail business loans if you are looking to establish a business. Based on your eligibility criteria and other requirements, you can avail loan amount of up to Rs.10 lakh under the Mudra Loan scheme, and Rs.5 crore under the MSME loan scheme. You can also apply for personal loan of up to Rs.20 lakh, home loan of up to Rs.10 crore, and auto loan of up to Rs. 1 crore as well.</string>
    <string name="like_mortgages_auto_loans_are_tied_toyour_property_they_can_help_you_afforda_vehicle_but_you_risk_losing_the_car_ifyou_miss_payments_this_type_of_loanmay_be_distributed_by_a_bank_or_by_thecar_dealership_directly_but_you_shouldunderstand_that_while_loans_from_thdealership_may_be_more_convenient_they_often_carry_higher_interest_rates_andultimately_cost_more_overall_an_auto_loan_is_taken_by_borrowersto_purchase_a_new_or_used_private_orcommercial_vehicle_auto_loans_are_securedloans_where_the_vehicle_itself_is_used_as_acollateral_it_is_offered_by_lenders_for_newcars_used_cars_two_wheelers_generallycalled_a_two_wheeler_loan_and_commercialvehicles_generally_called_a_commercialvehicle_loan_lenders_fix_interest_rates_depending_on_thetype_of_vehicle_and_loan_amount_interestrates_are_usually_fixed_for_auto_loans_it_is_not_always_necessary_to_go_with_thebank_your_vehicle_dealer_suggests_you_canalways_go_to_another_lender_if_they_offerbetter_loan_terms_therefore_always_do_athorough_research_by_comparing_lendersand_their_rates_before_finalizing_a_lender">Like mortgages, auto loans are tied toyour property. They can help you afforda vehicle, but you risk losing the car ifyou miss payments. This type of loanmay be distributed by a bank or by thecar dealership directly but you shouldunderstand that while loans from thdealership may be more convenient,they often carry higher interest rates andultimately cost more overall.An Auto Loan is taken by borrowersto purchase a new or used private orcommercial vehicle. Auto loans are securedloans where the vehicle itself is used as acollateral. It is offered by lenders for newcars, used cars, two wheelers (generallycalled a Two-wheeler Loan) and commercialvehicles (generally called a CommercialVehicle Loan).Lenders fix interest rates depending on thetype of vehicle and loan amount. Interestrates are usually fixed for auto loans.It is not always necessary to go with thebank your vehicle dealer suggests, you canalways go to another lender if they offerbetter loan terms. Therefore, always do athorough research by comparing lendersand their rates before finalizing a lender.</string>
    <string name="string">1. Check your credit To get a car loan, yourfirst step should be to check your creditreport and credit score. Your credit scoreis a number on a scale ranging from 300to 850 that looks at your borrowing historyto tell lenders how likely you are to repaywhat you borrow. It can be found for freethrough sites like Credit Karma. Your creditscore will have a big impact on the amountyou will pay to borrow, or the interest rateof your loan. There is no official minimumcredit score needed to buy a car, but thebest interest rates go to borrowers withcredit scores above 660. Knowing yourcredit score up front can help you tailor yourlender search to your specific situation, andavoid any surprises as you start shopping.2.Determine how much you need to borrow,and what you can afford This far in theprocess, you should already know whattype of car you are aiming to buy. Now isthe time to get more specific. You will wantto consider: The monthly payment. Howmuch can you afford to pay each month?How much you can put down. The rule ofthumb is a 20% down payment on a car.that may be worth a look. However, manylarger banks auto loans generally start witha higher interest rate than credit unionsOnline lenders. A number of online-onlybanks and lenders offer car loans. Whilethey can sometimes offer lower ratesdue to the fact that they donot have anyoverhead costs, there is no brick-and-mortaroffice to visit if that is important to you. 4Get pre-approved through those lendersOnce you have picked a few lenders, startapplying for pre-approvals. A pre-approvalis a bank is way of conditionally saying thatthey are willing to lend to you. You can getpre-approved by as many lenders as youwould like - you will want to check with afew lenders to compare the interest ratesthey offer. Dealerships can also help youarrange financing, but it is worth shoppingaround beforehand. It is common practicefor dealerships to mark up financing rates,so shopping around could help you besure that the dealership is offer is the bestdeal. 5. Compare your pre-approval offersOnce you start getting pre-approvals, youwill have two weeks to gather as manyis vou would like without having multipleThe more money you can put down upfront, the smaller the monthly payment willbe. How long a loan you will need. Longerloans may reduce the amount you oweeach month, but they could cause you to beupside down on your loan, a situation wherethe amount due on your loan is greaterthan the car is value. Cars are notoriousfor depreciation, or losing significant valueover time. Choose a loan that is 60 monthsor shorter to avoid an upside-down loan. Ifyour loan is too long, consider choosing aless expensive car, making a larger downpayment, or paying more each month. 3.Choose a few lenders you would like towork with Once you know how much youcan afford and your credit score, startlooking for a lender. A few options include:Credit unions. These local institutions oftenoffer low interest rates than large banks.You will have to become a member, andmembership is usually bound to things likegeographic location or an employer. Banks.Most banks also give loans like auto loans.Banks you already have a relationshipwith may offer you affordable rates, andthat may he worth a look However manyas you would like without having multiplehard credit inquiries appear on yourcredit report - they will all appear as one.Pre-approvals are generally good for 30 or60 days, depending on the lender. Compareyour pre-approval offers to find the offerthat best fits your monthly budget, carriesthe lowest APR or interest rate, and hasthe shortest term. 6. Accept an offer Nowis the time to accept the loan offer thatyou are happy with. Make sure you havethe proper documentation on hand, likeyour driver is license, proof of income,proof of insurance, and proof of residency,depending on the lender. You will also wantto bring the pre-approval paperwork andyour checkbook if you are making a downpayment. The bank will then arrange forthe funds or a blank check to be sent toyou or the dealership, and you are ready tobuy the car. 7. Head to the dealership Thisis the fun part: Pick out the car. Then, youwill sign some paperwork at the dealershipOftentimes, the lender you choose will sendyou a blank check, and you will fill it outonce you and the dealer have settled on aprice. You will make your down payment at</string>
    <string name="if_you_have_equity_in_your_home_the_house_is_worth_more_than_you_owe_on_it_you_can_use_that_equity_to_help_pay_for_big_projects_home_equity_loans_are_good_for_renovating_the_house_consolidating_credit_card_debt_paying_off_student_loans_and_many_other_worthwhile_projects_his_is_the_most_common_type_of_home_loan_availed_to_purchase_a_house_there_are_many_housing_finance_companies_public_banks_and_private_banks_that_offer_housing_loans_where_you_borrow_money_to_purchase_the_house_of_your_choice_and_repay_the_loan_n_monthly_instalments_you_can_get_up_to_80_90_of_the_houses_market_price_in_the_form_of_financing_the_lender_will_hold_the_house_until_you_completely_repay_the_loan_this_is_the_right_home_loan_type_if_you_already_have_a_plot_of_land_and_you_need_financing_to_construct_a_house_in_that_land_a_home_improvement_loan_provides_financing_for_renovating_or_repairing_the_house_if_there_s_any_fault_in_the_existing_system_such_as_painting_the_house_s_interior_or_exterior_plumbing_upgrading_the_electrical_system_waterproofing_the_ceiling_and_more">If you have equity in your home - the house is worth more than you owe on it - you can use that equity to help pay for big projects. Home equity loans are good for renovating the house, consolidating credit card debt, paying off student loans and many other worthwhile projects. his is the most common type of home loan availed to purchase a house. There are many housing finance companies, public banks, and private banks that offer housing loans where you borrow money to purchase the house of your choice and repay the loan n monthly instalments. You can get up to 80%-90% of the houses market price in the form of financing. The lender will hold the house until you completely repay the loan. This is the right home loan type if you already have a plot of land and you need financing to construct a house in that land. A home improvement loan provides financing for renovating or repairing the house if there\'s any fault in the existing system, such as painting the house\'s interior or exterior, plumbing, upgrading the electrical system, waterproofing the ceiling and more.</string>
    <string name="step_by_step_home_loan_procedure_step_1_filling_the_form_home_loan_procedure_starts_with_filling_out_the_loan_application_form_applying_for_a_home_loan_from_hdfc_bank_is_easy_following_are_the_basic_details_which_you_will_have_to_fill_in_the_form_name_address_contact_details_phone_number_and_email_id_education_type_of_employment_salaried_or_self_employed_income_earned_step_2_documentation_once_you_fill_in_your_basic_details_you_will_have_to_attach_the_following_documents_for_verification_identity_proof_pan_card_aadhar_card_voter_id_driving_license_address_of_proof_can_be_a_copy_of_any_utility_bill_salary_slips_of_the_last_3_months_proof_of_employment_bank_statements_of_the_last_6_months_form_16_note_if_you_are_a_self_employed_individual_you_need_to_provide_the_itr_of_the_last_2_years_and_the_other_income_documents_step_3_processing_and_verification_on_submission_of_the_form_along_with_the_required_documents_the_bank_starts_processing_your_home_loan_application_the_bank_will_verify_all_the_documents_provided_by_you_workplace_or_home_for_the_same_the_next_step_is_checking_your_creditworthiness_as_a_borrower_the_bank_conducts_an_extensive_enquiry_into_your_credit_score_hence_it_is_important_that_you_maintain_a_healthy_credit_history_if_all_your_documents_are_in_order_and_you_have_a_satisfactory_credit_score_and_report_the_bank_will_proceed_with_your_loan_application_step_4_sanction_letter_on_successful_approval_of_your_home_loan_application_the_bank_will_send_you_a_sanction_letter_this_letter_acts_as_proof_that_the_bank_has_approved_your_loan_all_essential_details_about_the_loan_transaction_are_enclosed_in_this_letter_such_as_the_loan_amount_you_are_eligible_for_the_interest_rate_offered_whether_the_interest_rate_is_fixed_or_variable_tenure_of_repayment_terms_and_conditions_of_repayment_read_more_about_fixed_or_floating_interest_rates_for_home_loans_here_after_carefully_reviewing_all_the_points_mentioned_in_the_sanction_letter_you_can_sign_the_letter_and_send_it_back_to_the_bank_only_after_the_bank_receives_the_signed_letter_from_you_the_home_loan_procedure_moves_to_the_next_step_legal_and_technical_check_before_the_bank_disburses_the_loan_amount_it_conducts_legal_and_technical_checks_the_bank_representatives_will_verify_the_property_you_have_applied_the_loan_for_they_will_check_if_the_ownership_rights_of_the_property_are_transparent_the_representatives_will_also_check_if_the_documents_submitted_and_the_proofs_provided_have_any_conflicting_information_during_the_technical_check_the_bank_representatives_will_evaluate_the_actual_value_of_the_property_the_status_of_the_property_under_construction_or_resale_will_also_be_taken_into_consideration_if_the_property_is_under_construction_they_will_check_the_construction_stage_and_quality_of_the_work_whereas_if_the_property_is_a_resale_one_the_bank_will_check_the_age_and_maintenance_of_the_property_in_case_of_the_resale_the_bank_may_also_check_if_the_property_has_already_been_mortgaged_before_step_7_loan_disbursal_once_the_bank_is_satisfied_with_the_checks_conducted_your_home_loan_application_will_be_approved_you_will_receive_a_final_agreement_letter_post_loan_disbursal_you_will_receive_a_welcome_kit_and_a_detailed_housing_loan_approved_you_will_receive_a_final_agreement_letter_post_loan_disbursal_you_will_receive_a_welcome_kit_and_a_detailed_housing_loan_emi_schedule_it_is_important_that_you_check_whether_you_meet_the_required_home_loan_eligibility_criteria_before_applying_for_the_loan_you_can_seek_professional_guidance_here_to_make_a_more_informed_decision_if_you_already_are_a_borrower_and_want_to_switch_your_lender_you_can_opt_for_the_home_loan_transfer_procedure">Step by step - Home Loan Procedure Step 1: Filling the form Home Loan Procedure starts with filling out the loan application form. Applying for a Home Loan from HDFC Bank is easy. Following are the basic details which you will have to fill in the form: Name Address Contact details - phone number and email ID Education Type of employment - salaried or self-employed Income earned Step 2: Documentation Once you fill in your basic details, you will have to attach the following documents for verification: Identity proof - PAN card/ Aadhar Card / Voter ID/ Driving license Address of proof - can be a copy of any utility bill Salary slips of the last 3 months Proof of employment Bank statements of the last 6 months Form 16 Note: If you are a self-employed individual, you need to provide the ITR of the last 2 years and the other income documents. Step 3: Processing and Verification On submission of the form along with the required documents, the bank starts processing your Home Loan application. The bank will verify all the documents provided by you. workplace or home for the same. The next step is checking your creditworthiness as a borrower. The bank conducts an extensive enquiry into your credit score. Hence it is important that you maintain a healthy credit history. If all your documents are in order and you have a satisfactory credit score and report, the bank will proceed with your loan application. Step 4: Sanction Letter On successful approval of your Home Loan application, the bank will send you a sanction letter. This letter acts as proof that the bank has approved your loan. All essential details about the loan transaction are enclosed in this letter, such as: The loan amount you are eligible for. The interest rate offered. Whether the interest rate is fixed or variable. Tenure of repayment. Terms and conditions of repayment. Read more about fixed or floating interest rates for Home Loans here. After carefully reviewing all the points mentioned in the sanction letter, you can sign the letter and send it back to the bank. Only after the bank receives the signed letter from you, the Home Loan procedure moves to the next step. Legal and Technical Check Before the bank disburses the loan amount, it conducts legal and technical checks. The bank representatives will verify the property you have applied the loan for. They will check if the ownership rights of the property are transparent. The representatives will also check if the documents submitted, and the proofs provided have any conflicting information. During the technical check, the bank representatives will evaluate the actual value of the property. The status of the property - under construction or resale - will also be taken into consideration. If the property is under construction, they will check the construction stage and quality of the work. Whereas, if the property is a resale one, the bank will check the age and maintenance of the property. In case of the resale, the bank may also check if the property has already been mortgaged before. Step 7: Loan Disbursal Once the bank is satisfied with the checks conducted, your Home Loan application will be approved. You will receive a final agreement letter. Post loan disbursal, you will receive a welcome kit and a detailed housing loan approved. You will receive a final agreement letter. Post loan disbursal, you will receive a welcome kit and a detailed housing loan EMI schedule. It is important that you check whether you meet the required Home Loan eligibility criteria before applying for the loan. You can seek professional guidance here to make a more informed decision. If you already are a borrower and want to switch your lender, you can opt for the Home Loan Transfer procedure.</string>
    <string name="to_promote_small_enterprises_in_the_country_the_government_has_introduced_several_loan_schemes_apart_from_the_pradhan_mantri_mudra_yojana_there_are_many_other_schemes_in_which_you_can_take_small_loans_to_big_loans_1010_at_this_time_according_to_the_schemes_of_the_central_and_state_government_you_can_take_a_loan_of_rs_50_000_o_rs_1_lakh_for_your_business_1010_actually_banks_decide_to_give_you_a_loan_according_to_your_business_plan_if_the_bank_feels_that_your_business_and_profits_from_it_will_be_so_much_that_you_will_be_able_to_repay_the_loan_of_the_bank_within_the_stipulated_period_after_completing_your_expenses_only_then_the_bank_approves_your_loan_1010_what_are_the_benefits_of_taking_a_business_loan_financial_support_for_inward_business_needs_of_cash_to_meet_financial_needs_for_both_short_and_long_term_a_bank_loan_may_be_obtained_from_a_bank_and_may_be_either_secured_or_unsecured_for_secured_loans_banks_will_require_collateral_which_may_be_lost_if_repayments_are_not_made_the_bank_will_probably_wish_to_see_the_business_s_accounts_balance_sheet_and_business_plan_as_well_as_studying_the_principals_credit_histories_many_smaller_businesses_are_now_however_turning_towards_alternative_finance_providers_especially_in_the_case_of_smaller_firms">To promote small enterprises in the country, the government has introduced several loan schemes. Apart from the Pradhan Mantri Mudra Yojana, there are many other schemes in which you can take small loans to big loans. 1010 At this time, according to the schemes of the central and state government, you can take a loan of Rs 50,000 o Rs 1 lakh for your business. 1010 Actually banks decide to give you a loan according to your business plan. If the bank feels that your business and profits from it will be so much that you will be able to repay the loan of the bank within the stipulated period after completing your expenses, only then the bank approves your loan.1010 What are the benefits of taking a business loan? Financial support for inward business needs of cash to meet financial needs for both short and long term. A bank loan may be obtained from a bank and may be either secured or unsecured. For secured loans, banks will require collateral, which may be lost if repayments are not made. The bank will probably wish to see the business\'s accounts, balance sheet and business plan, as well as studying the principals\' credit histories. Many smaller businesses are now however turning towards Alternative Finance Providers, especially in the case of smaller firms.</string>
    <string name="student_loans_are_offered_to_college_studentsand_their_families_tohigher_education_there_are_two_main_types_federal_student_loans_and_private_studentloans_federally_funded_loans_are_better_asthey_typically_come_with_lower_interest_ratesand_more_borrower_friendly_repaymentterms_an_education_loan_is_a_sum_of_moneyborrowed_to_finance_post_secondaryeducation_or_higher_education_relatedexpenses_education_loans_are_intendedto_cover_the_cost_of_tuition_books_andsupplies_and_living_expenses_while_thedegree_payments_are_often_deferred_whilestudents_are_in_college_and_depending_onthe_lender_sometimes_they_are_deferredfor_an_additional_six_month_period_afterearning_a_degree_this_period_is_sometimesreferred_to_as_a_graceperiod_educationloans_are_issued_for_the_purpose_of_attendingan_accredited_college_or_a_university_andpursuing_an_academic_degree_educationloans_can_be_obtained_from_the_governmentor_through_private_sector_lendingsources_federal_loans_often_offer_lowerinterest_rates_and_some_also_offer_subsidizedinterest_private_sector_loans_generallyfollow_more_of_a_traditional_lending_processfor_application_with_rates_that_are_typicallyhigher_than_federal_government_loans">Student loans are offered to college studentsand their families tohigher education. There are two main types:federal student loans and private studentloans. Federally funded loans are better, asthey typically come with lower interest ratesand more borrower-friendly repaymentterms.An education loan is a sum of moneyborrowed to finance post-secondaryeducation or higher education-relatedexpenses. Education loans are intendedto cover the cost of tuition, books andsupplies, and living expenses while thedegree. Payments are often deferred whilestudents are in college and, depending onthe lender, sometimes they are deferredfor an additional six-month period afterearning a degree. This period is sometimesreferred to as a graceperiod.Educationloans are issued for the purpose of attendingan accredited college or a university andpursuing an academic degree. Educationloans can be obtained from the governmentor through private-sector lendingsources.Federal loans often offer lowerinterest rates, and some also offer subsidizedinterest. Private-sector loans generallyfollow more of a traditional lending processfor application, with rates that are typicallyhigher than federal government loans.</string>
    <string name="student">Student loans are offered to college studentsand their families to help cover the face tohigher education. There are two main types:federal student loans and private studentloans. Federally funded loans are better, asthey typically come with lower interest ratesand more borrower-friendly repaymentterms.An education loan is a sum of moneyborrowed to finance post-secondaryeducation or higher education-relatedexpenses. Education loans are intendedto cover the cost of tuition, books andsupplies, and living expenses while theborrower is in the process of pursuing adegree. Payments are often deferred whilestudents are in college and, depending onthe lender, sometimes they are deferredfor an additional six-month period afterearning a degree. This period is sometimesreferred to as a grace period.Educationloans are issued for the purpose of attendingan accredited college or a university andpursuing an academic degree. Educationloans can be obtained from the governmentor through private-sector lendingsources.Federal loans often offer lowerinterest rates, and some also offer subsidizedinterest. Private-sector loans generallyfollow more of a traditional lending processfor application, with rates that are typicallyhigher than federal government loans.applications (including applicationsreceived by Bank in physical format) areto be applied through Vidya Lakshmiportal, i.e. https://www.vidyalakshmi.coin/Students Step 2 - Interview The nextstep in the education loan procedure isthe interview round. After considering yourapplication, your bank typically calls youfor a personal discussion or an interview.Note that the loan is offered to the studentand co-obligation of parents/ guardianand the student is considered as the mainloan applicant. You may be asked severalquestions pertaining to your academicperformance, the institute you wish toattend, the course selected by you, futurescope of your chosen course and so on.You must be honest and should be able toconvince the bank that you are choosing astream that has the potential to generategood income, thus enabling you to repaythe loan. Step 3 - Documentation Beforethe loan is processed you need to proveto the bank that your chosen universityhas extended an offer of admission. Thisis the primary document that all banksask for, even before one begins the actualloan application process. The bank canget in touch with the university to verifyyour enrolment. If your education loanamount exceeds $4,00,000, you would berequired to provide some sort of collateralin the form of third party Guarantee if therequired loan amount is upto Rs. 7,50,000,and if it exceeds 7,50,000 you are requiredto provide collateral security equivalentto 100 % of the loan amount along withassignment of future income of the studentfor payment of instalments. Assignment offuture income of the student for paymentof instalments is applicable to all EducationLoans irrespective of Loan amount. Step4 - Loan approval As per the educationloan repayment procedure, banks offer theloan to the student applicant, and sincethe student cannot repay the loan until thecourse is completed, the bank considersparents/guardians as co-borrower ofthe loan. the bank also verifies the credithistory of the co-borrower/guarantorbefore sanctioning the loan. bank offersmoratorium period equivalent to thecourse period plus year and it is optionalfor the borrowers to serve the interesteducation loan during this moratoriumperiod. the loan is approved, the borrowerswill receive a sanction letter from thebank. the borrowers accept the terms andconditions of sanction, bank calls themfor execution of loan documents and handover of collateral security papers in originalto the bank if it is required as per terms ofStep 5 - Loan disbursal The final step inthe education bank loan procedure is loandisbursal. Banks typically directly disbursethe loan to your chosen university by wayof Banker\'s cheque, Demand draft or SWIFTmessage as per the location of the chosenUniversity/Institution along with yourmargin if stipulated in Sanction.</string>
    <string name="mortgages">Mortgages are loans distributed by banksto allow consumers to buy homes they can\'tpay for upfront. A mortgage is tied to yourhome, meaning you risk foreclosure if youfall behind on payments. Mortgages haveamong the lowest interest rates of all loans.Mortgage refers to the process of offeringsomething as a guarantee or collateralagainst a loan. One may come acrossthe term when looking for securedloans.Generally, home loans of all types aresecured loans. The borrower must offertheir property as a security to the lenderThe property mortgaged acts as collateraluntil the borrower has repaid the loan infull. Mortgage loans are also commonlyknown as loans against property.A mortgageloan can be used to either buy or build ahouse or refinance a property. Refinancingrefers to getting a new loan for a propertywhile the original loan is still being repaidIt is usually done to get a loan with betterterms.A simple mortgage is an agreementthat if the borrower is unable to repay theloan in full, the lender can sell the propertythat was offered as collateral and recovertheir amount. However, the property is nottransferred to the lender. The collateral cancome under the possession of the lender ifthe borrower fails to make full repayment ofthe loan during the tenure originally agreedupon.</string>
    <string name="mortgagess"><![CDATA[There are broadly eight steps to the loanapplication process: 1. Fill up the homeloan Application Form: Every would-beborrower, like Dinesh, has to fill up ahome loan application form. This willinvolve information like name, address,income details and prodetails, education details, and phonenumber. Dinesh will also have to furnishproofs for all the above as well as salaryslips-for the latest 3 months, employmentproof, bank statements - for the latest6 months and the latest Form 16, sincehe is a salaried employee. Self-employedborrowers will have to provide the full setof ITR returns for the last two years alongwith other income documents. 2. Pay theProcessing Fee: After Dinesh submitshis documents he has to pay the initialprocessing fee as decided by the bank,which is non-refundable. This is chargedfor the preliminary work the bank does toverify borrower details and to investigatethe property\'s value and ownership title.The remaining processing fee is takenater on at the time of disbursement. ButDinesh\'s loan will not be approved justbecause he has paid these fees. The feesvary from bank to bank. It may be either afixed amount or a percentage of the loanamount. Axis Bank, for example, chargesa fee up to 1% of the loan amount (witha minimum of Rs. 10,000+ applicabletaxes). 3. Bank Discussion: The bankusually takes a decision as per bank creditpolicy on whether to approve or rejectthe loan application within 5 workingdays. The bank may call Dinesh for atelephonic discussion. This is the casefor most salaried employees. In caseof self-employed borrowers, the bank\'srepresentative may visit the customer\'splace of work for personal discussion andto understand about their business. Thiswill help the credit underwriter to upraiseloan in a better way. [Also Read: HomeLoan Balance Transfer - All You Need ToKnow] 4. Document Verification: Once thebank completes the personal discussionwith Dinesh, it will start calculating hiseligibility. This could involve a bank officialvisiting his current residence and/or gettingin touch with his employers. The bank willcheck Dinesh is credit score with a bureaulike CIBIL. 5. Approval Process: This is theprocess (as per Bank Credit Policy) that willdecide if the bank will approve Dinesh\'s loanapplication. Dinesh has to make sure thatall his documents are in order; otherwise,his application may get rejected. 6Sanction Letter: The bank will send Dinesha loan sanction letter if his loan is approved.This letter will contain Dinesh\'s eligible loanamount, interest rate and type (fixed orvariable) applicable, loan tenure with terms& condition. If Dinesh accepts it, he hasto sign it and send a copy to the bank. 7.Property Verification: Now that the loan hasbeen approved and accepted, the bank willverify the property. It will do a legal checkon the property to ensure the title is clearand there is no dispute or conflict regardingthe same. It will also conduct a technicalvaluation on the property. If the property isunder construction, it will check the stage,progress and quality of construction aswell. If the property is a resale property,the bank will check the age, quality andmaintenance levels of the building. Itwill also check if the property is alreadymortgaged. Dinesh will have to submit allproperty papers, including original copiesof the title deed, to the bank. These papersare mortgaged with the bank until Dineshrepays the loan in full. 8. Loan Disbursal:Once the property verification is complete,the customer has to provide all documentsas per legal and technical reports.Following this loan agreement is signedand if all documents are in order, the loanwill get disbursed and the cheque will behanded over to the customer. The chequemay be made in favour of the builder, if youare purchasing the property from a builder.Post-disbursement, the bank will send thecustomer the welcome kit, along with therepayment schedule. The EMI payment isdone either through Standing Instructions,if the account from which payment is beingmade is from the same bank, or throughNACH mandate - if the account from whichpayment is being made is with anotherbank. (NACH or Nationalised AutomatedClearing House Payment Solution is thecentralised system that facilitates theseamless transactions between banks).]]></string>
    <string name="payday">Payday loans are short-term, high-interestloans designed to bridge the gap from onepaycheck to the next, used predominantlyby repeat borrowers living paycheckto paycheck. The government stronglydiscourages consumers from taking outpayday loans because of their high costs andinterest rates.A payday loan is a type of short-termborrowing where a lender will extendhigh-interest credit based on your income.Its principal is typically a portion of yournext paycheck. Payday loans charge highinterest rates for short-term immediatecredit. They are also called cash advanceloans or check advance loans. Payday loanproviders will normally require you toshow proof of your income-usually yourpay stubs from your employer. They willthen lend you a portion of the money thatyou will be paid. You will have to pay theloan back within a short time, generally 30days or less. Payday lenders take on a lot ofrisk, because they don\'t check your abilityto pay back the loan. Because of this, theynormally charge very high interest ratesfor payday loans, and they may also chargehigh fees if you miss your repayments. Thiscan be dangerous for borrowers, becauseit can mean that you\'ll need to borrowmore money to cover the cost of the firstloan.Payday loan providers are typicallysmall credit merchants with physical storesthat allow on-site credit applications andapproval. Some payday loan services also may be available through online lenders.</string>
    <string name="paydayy">Payday loans are short-term, high-interestloans designed to bridge the gap from onepaycheck to the next, used predominantlyby repeat borrowers living paycheckto paycheck. The government stronglydiscourages consumers from taking outpayday loans because of their high costs andinterest rates.A payday loan is a type of short-termborrowing where a lender will extendhigh-interest credit based on your income.Its principal is typically a portion of yournext paycheck. Payday loans charge highinterest rates for short-term immediatecredit. They are also called cash advanceloans or check advance loans. Payday loanproviders will normally require you toshow proof of your income-usually yourpay stubs from your employer. They willthen lend you a portion of the money thatyou will be paid. You will have to pay theloan back within a short time, generally 30days or less. Payday lenders take on a lot ofrisk, because they don\'t check your abilityto pay back the loan. Because of this, theynormally charge very high interest ratesfor payday loans, and they may also chargehigh fees if you miss your repayments. Thiscan be dangerous for borrowers, becauseit can mean that you\'ll need to borrowmore money to cover the cost of the firstloan.Payday loan providers are typicallysmall credit merchants with physical storesthat allow on-site credit applications andapproval. Some payday loan services alsousually deposit the funds on the nextbusiness day following the approval;however, some lenders may take up totwo days to process your application anddeposit your funds. Step 4 - Agree to thefees and terms Once you have completedyour application, review all of the fees andterms. If everything is correct, proceedto click submit or next to complete yourapplication. This will send it directly toa lender for review. You should receivean instant response from a lender aboutwhether you have been approved for theloan. How to choose a payday loan lender?If you are thinking of applying for paydayloans, then it is important that you searchonly through reputed lending companiesthat offer fair interest rates and transparentterms and conditions. Here are some tipson how to choose a reputable paydaylender: 1. A reputable payday lender mustnot charge any upfront fees. 2. A reputablepayday lender will not engage in any sortof coercion or harassment if you rejecttheir offer to provide you with a loan. 3. Areputable payday lender should be able toend you money even if your credit score isnot charge any upfront fees. 2. A reputablepayday lender will not engage in any sortof coercion or harassment if you rejecttheir offer to provide you with a loan. 3. Areputable payday lender should be able tolend you money even if your credit score islow. 4. A reputable payday lender will nevercharge hidden fees. 5. Look for customertestimonials online to see what othercustomers are saying about the companiesservice, pricing and convenience</string>
    <string name="smallBusiness">Everyone\'s dream is to have a branded carwith them at home. A car not only makesyour life comfortable, but also reduces manydifficulties. Reaching the office while battlingpublic transport or going out for weekends,everything becomes very easy.1010 Earlier,buying a car was a big thing for anyone,because it had to spend a lump sum, but nowit is very easy due to the easy availabilityof a car loan.1010 Banks and non-bankingfinance companies offer car loans on easymonthly installments, which has made itvery easy to buy cars. Due to this, yourbudget is not deteriorated and convenienceis also available.Payday loan providers are typically smallcredit merchants with physical storesthat allow on-site credit applications andapproval. Some payday loan servicesalso may be available through onlinelenders. Payday loan providers are typicallysmall credit merchants with physicalstores that allow on-site credit applicationsand approval. Some payday loan servicesalso may be available through onlinelenders. Payday loan providers are typicallysmall credit merchants with physicalstores that allow on-site credit applicationsand approval. Some payday loan servicesalso may be available through onlinelenders. Payday loan providers are typicallysmall credit merchants with physical storesthat allow on-site credit applications andapproval. Some payday loan services alsomay be available through online lenders.</string>
    <string name="smallbusines"><![CDATA[If you determine that it\'s best to go thesmall business loan application route, learnhow to apply for a small business loanusing these seven steps. 1. Determine howmuch you need First things first, determinehow much of a loan you need by listingout what you need the funds for. You mayneed a small business loan to: Start yourbusiness Expand Purchase equipmentIncrease inventory Improve cash flow Whatyou need the funds for can vary dependingon what stage of life your business is in(e.g., startup). To determine the ideal loanamount for your business, make a list ofwhat you plan on using the funds for. Then,do a little research to help guesstimatehow much in loans you\'ll need to coverthe costs. 2. Review your credit score andhistory Part of the loan process includeslenders looking at your credit history andscore. And in many cases, lenders maylook at both personal and business creditinformation. It\'s a good rule of thumb tolook at where your credit stands beforeyou start applying for any type of loan-specially if you\'re a newer business owner.Before applying for a small business loan,check out your credit history and score. Youcan request a credit score from an agency(e.g., Dun & Bradstreet). Or, you may beable to get a good idea of where your creditstands from reports from your bank andcredit card companies. Review your creditreports after you gather them. And, checkout your credit score. A personal scoreof 700 or more is generally consideredgood (300 - 850 range). However, manyenders will want to see a minimum scoreof 680. A good business credit score istypically 75 or above (0 - 100 range). Thehigher your credit score and the betteryour credit history, the more likely youare to receive a loan. 3. Review your loanoptions There are a variety of loan optionsto choose from nowadays. Before you startshopping around for a lender and applyingfor a loan, you need to know the differenttypes. Many loans are designed for certaintypes of businesses or specific financialsituations. Here are a few types of businessloans to look into: 4. Check out your localSCORE and SBDC offices If you\'re a newerbusiness. vou may want to consideroffices. Small Business DevelopmentCenter (SBDC) and SCORE provideconfidential advice to small businessesacross the country. SCORE consists ofa retired group of business executiveswho can provide one-on-one guidance tobusiness owners. SBDC, part of the SmallBusiness Administration, also exists tohelp small businesses. Both organizationscan help assist you with the businessloan application process and answer anyquestions you may have. 5. Determinewhich type of lender is the best fit for youWhen it comes to getting a small businessloan, you have a number of options. You\'renot tied down to only getting a loan from aarge, national bank. You can also receivea loan from a smaller lender. Here are afew types of lenders you can choose from:Banks Credit unions Nonprofit lendersOnline lenders Microlenders The lender youmay go with can vary depending on the typeof loan you want (think back to Step #3).Before choosing a lender, do your research.Look at factors like interest rates and totalborrowing costs. And, be sure to look atreviews to see what other clients have tosay. 6. Gather necessary documents Afteryou narrow down which lender you wantto go with, find out what documentationthe lender requires for a loan. Generally,you may need to provide the followinginformation: Business plan Financialstatements Business banking accountBank statements Business license andpermits Identification (e.g., driver\'s licenseOther business documents (e.g., articlesof incorporation) Business tax returns Ifyou\'re a new business, you may not haveall of the above information yet. Beforeyou apply for a loan, make sure you findout what information you need and whataccounts you must set up. Each lender hasts own requirements and eligibility criteria.So, check with your potential lender to findout what specific information you need togather. 7. Complete your application Gatherall of your necessary documents? Great!Now comes the fun part: Submitting yourapplication and officially applying for theloan. Book an appointment with a lender toget the ball rolling on your business loanapplication. Depending on your lender, youmay be able to apply online or over thephone. However, many lenders require youto fill out a paper application in person.Whatever method your lender allows, makesure you have your documents handy (e.g.,business licenses and permits, ID, etc.).Once you complete your application, itwill go through an underwriting processwith the lender. An underwriting processverifies your information (e.g., income,debt, credit, etc.) to issue an approval forthe loan. The application, underwriting, andfunding process may take anywhere from afew days to a few months. Check with yourlender to get an estimate of how long theprocess will take before you can receive aloan. In some cases, you may need to makea pitch to your loan officer or lender on whythey should trust your business with theloan money. This is where your businessplan can come into play. To ensure you\'reprepared, rehearse and plan your talkingpoints.]]></string>
    <string name="splashtext">Get approved With \n an easy online loan application!</string>
    <string name="guidelinee">All kind loan which document wanted and which financial\n institunion supplied this app mortgage all in clean to guide where is\n this is finicial institution and his department easy to reveal in inner</string>
    <string name="guideline">We provide the bank guide lines that how you\n easy apply for loan and quickly get the loan approval\n from the any bank.</string>
    <string name="calculator">Loan &amp; Finance Planner</string>
    <string name="bannerid">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/6300978111</string>
</resources>